cfd-online.com 2018-12-22

# CFD Online - Privacy Policy

Home > CFD Online - Privacy Policy

_Last updated: September 12, 2017_

CFD Online AB ("us", "we", or "our") operates the website https://www.cfd-online.com (the "Site"). This page informs you about our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information that we receive from users of the Site. 

We use your Personal Information only for providing and running the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. 

### Information Collected

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name and your email address ("Personal Information"). 

Like many site operators, we collect the information that your browser sends when you visit our Site ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's IP address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this. 

### Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

We will only use your Personal Information to operate the Site. Examples of use is password-reset emails, emails about forum threads that you are subscribed to, weekly email news-digests that you have registered to receive, information about very important Site news, like security breaks. We will not disclose your Personal Information unless you explicitly enter it in a publicly visible position on our Site. **Your privacy is important to us and we will not use your Personal Information for marketing and we will never sell or give your Personal Information to anyone else, unless required by law.**

By default registered forum members are visible and the public parts of their profile can be seen by all visitors. This includes set Real Name, Location, Contact Information and more. Your email address will not be visible though. Forum users can themself change their profile privacy and modify their forum options to set if other visitors should be able to see their profile and contact them via private messages or via email.

We will use the Log Data collected to generate statistics for the traffic on our site. The Log Data may also be used to identify, track and block persons or IP addresses that post spam or in any other way affect our ability to provide a good service to our normal visitors. Individual Log Data for users who behave and do not break the forum rules will not be disclosed to anyone. 

### Cookies

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information and improve your interaction with our Site. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions or functions on our Site. 

### Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. We use SSL encrypted communication in order to reduce the risk of someone else being able to intercept your Personal Information. We strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, however, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of September 12, 2017. We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by placing a prominent notice on our Site News & Announcements section. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
